spaweek.com 2019-02-04

# Spa & Wellness Gift Cards, Spa Discounts, Spa Deals, and Spa Packages from Spa Week | Spa Week

## Spa Week Media - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting this Spa Week Media Group, Ltd. ("SWMG") Internet web site ("Site") located at the URL www.spaweek.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout SWMG governing SWMG's use of personally identifiable information about users of our Site.

Privacy Policy Updates Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, SWMG may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, SWMG will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site and we may send registered users an email of the change. SWMG encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes so that you are aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. If any modification is unacceptable to you, you shall cease using this Site. If you do not cease using this Site, you will be deemed to have accepted the change.

Information Collection and Use You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site, we may invite you to contact us with questions or comments or request information, subscribe to a newsletter or mailing list, participate in giveaway programs or chat boards, purchase products and services, or complete a registration form. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, contact data such as your address, phone number, email address, gender, age, income level, job, username, password and credit card information and any other personally identifiable information you elect to include in your communications sent to us or in your postings to the Site. If you purchase a gift certificate or card, you will be asked to provide the name of the recipient of the gift certificate or card.

We may use your personally identifiable information to register you to use our Site, deliver certain goods, services or information you have requested, process your payment, administer our giveaways programs, provide you with notices regarding goods or services you have purchased, send you newsletters and information you have requested and improve the content and general administration of the Site. Other users will be able to view the username of users that have posted information, content and ratings to the Site.

As you browse www.spaweek.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with [company website]. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this page (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of this targeted advertising.

Children's Privacy SWMG recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. This Site is not intended for children under the age of 13 and we endeavor not to collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. SWMG targets its services and this Site to adults and not to children under 13.

Aggregate Information The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site and your movement on this Site and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed to third parties in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer and improve the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Disclosure We may provide your personally identifiable information and the aggregate information to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us in providing our services to you. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to a credit card processing company to process your payments. We may provide your personally identifiable information to third party entities with which we have a business relationship when you have provided your consent to such transfer of your personally identifiable information to such third parties by opting-in at the point where we collect your personally identifiable information and without your prior consent as we determine for the third parties' own marketing purposes as described in Your California Privacy Rights.

We also will disclose your personally identifiable information when we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, or when we deem it appropriate or necessary to provide such information to law enforcement authorities. We may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which SWMG participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of SWMG's assets to which this Site relates.

Links to Third Party Sites The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which SWMG does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by SWMG of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that SWMG is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that SWMG is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

Security We may employ procedural and technological security measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. SWMG may use other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

Users Outside of the United States Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your personal data will be processed by us in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you use this Site from outside the United States, you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection of that required in the European Union or certain other countries, and to the processing of that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Questions If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via email at info@spaweek.com

This Privacy Policy is effective as of: August 21, 2008

## Cookie Policy

**Last updated May 10, 2018**

This Cookie Policy explains how Spa Week Media Group, Ltd. and Spa Week Media Group, Ltd., (collectively " **SWMG** ", " **we** ", " **us** ", and " **ours** ") use cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you visit our websites at www.spaweek.com, blog.spaweek.com, (" **Websites** "). It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.

In some cases we may use cookies to collect personal information, or that becomes personal information if we combine it with other information. In such cases our Privacy Policy (https://www.spaweek.com/privacy-policy) will apply in addition to this Cookie Policy. 

## What are cookies?

Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.

Cookies set by the website owner (in this case, SWMG) are called "first party cookies". Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called "third party cookies". Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g. like advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites.

## Why do we use cookies?

We use first and third party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Websites to operate, and we refer to these as "essential" or "strictly necessary" cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Online Properties. Third parties serve cookies through our Websites for advertising, analytics and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.

The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit): 

### Essential website cookies:

These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our Websites and to use some of its features, such as access to secure areas.

**Who serves these cookies:**

• Cookie provider: Rakuten Marketing 

Website URL: https://rakutenmarketing.com/affiliate

• Cookie provider: Annex Cloud 

Website URL: https://www.annexcloud.com/

• Cookie provider: Sailthru 

Website URL: https://www.sailthru.com/ 

• Cookie provider: Google Analytics 

Website URL: https://analytics.google.com/ 

• Cookie provider: Facebook 

Website URL: https://www.facebook.com/ 

■ HOW TO REFUSE: Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the Websites to you, you cannot refuse them. You can block or delete them by changing your browser settings however, as described below under the heading "How can I control cookies? (#control) ". 

### Analytics and customization cookies:

These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our Website are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our Websites for you.

■ WHO SERVES THESE COOKIES: 

• Cookie provider: Google Analytics 

Website URL: https://analytics.google.com/ 

■ HOW TO REFUSE: To refuse these cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies? (#control) ". Alternatively, please visit the relevant opt-out link below: 

• Cookie provider: Google Analytics 

Opt-out Link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout 

### Social networking cookies:

These cookies are used to enable you to share pages and content that you find interesting on our Websites through third party social networking and other websites. These cookies may also be used for advertising purposes too.

■ WHO SERVES THESE COOKIES: 

• Cookie provider: Annex Cloud 

Website URL: http://www.annexcloud.com 

■ HOW TO REFUSE: To refuse these cookies, please follow the instructions below under the heading "How can I control cookies? (#control) ". Alternatively, please visit the relevant opt-out link below: 

• Cookie provider: Annex Cloud 

Opt-out Link: http://www.annexcloud.com/privacy-policy 

## What about other tracking technologies, like web beacons?

Cookies are not the only way to recognize or track visitors to a website. We may use other, similar technologies from time to time, like web beacons (sometimes called "tracking pixels" or "clear gifs"). These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enable us to recognize when someone has visited our Websites or opened an e-mail that we have sent them. This allows us, for example, to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within our Websites to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to our Websites from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, to improve site performance, and to measure the success of e-mail marketing campaigns. In many instances, these technologies are reliant on cookies to function properly, and so declining cookies will impair their functioning. 

## How can I control cookies?

You can set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website though your access to some functionality and areas of our website may be restricted. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information.

In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or http://www.youronlinechoices.com.

## How often will you update this Cookie Policy?

We may update this Cookie Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Please therefore re-visit this Cookie Policy regularly to stay informed about our use of cookies and related technologies. 

The date at the top of this Cookie Policy indicates when it was last updated.

## Where can I get further information?

If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at info@spaweekmedia.com or by post to:

Spa Week Media Group, Ltd. 

89 5th Ave 

4th Flr

New York, NY 10003
